My dear friend, you must be wondering
Sevgili dostum, merak ediyor olmalısın
Why I'm leaving you a letter like this
sana neden böyle bir mektup bıraktığımı.
It's because...
Çünkü...
Hey, Gulab! I'm here. How are you feeling today?
Hey, Gulab! Buradayım. Nasılsın bugün?
I gotta tell you, I had an idea for another card last night
Dün gece aklıma bir kart fikri geldi, sana anlatmam gerek.
Huh? What's that you're writing?
Ha? Ne yazıyorsun öyle?
Haha, it's nothing
Haha, bir şey değil.
Okay... Anyway, up for a game?
Peki... Neyse, oyun oynayalım mı?
You don't have to visit every day, you know. You should be focusing on your work at the Akademiya...
Her gün gelmene gerek yok, biliyorsun. Akademideki çalışmalarına odaklanman gerek...
Hey, enough of that, I'll keep visiting until you've fully recovered
Hey, yeter ama. Sen tamamen iyileşene kadar geleceğim.
Besides, I can't stand most of the folks at the Akademiya anyway!
Akademidekilere katlanamıyorum nasıl olsa!
Hey, it's your turn
Hey, senin sıran.
*coughing*
*öksürür*
Gulab!? Are you okay?
Gulab! İyi misin?
*cough* Garvipidam, you must understand...
*öksürür* Garvipidam, anlaman gerek...
My Eleazar...
Eleazar hastalığım...
Hey! Don't talk like that!
Hey! Böyle konuşma!
You just need some more rest...
Sadece dinlenmen gerek...
*sigh*...
*iç çeker*
It's because... you won't come to terms with the fact that I don't have long left
Çünkü... Artık vaktimin kalmadığını kabullenemiyorsun.
Guess what? This game we invented
Bil bakalım ne oldu? Birlikte bulduğumuz oyun
Is getting pretty popular here in the hospital
hastanede gittikçe popüler hale geliyor.
Really? That's great news!
Gerçekten mi? Bu harika bir haber.
Yeah. I've even made a device
Evet. Hatta bir cihaz bile yaptım.
To help people find other players nearby
Diğer oyuncuları bulmaya yarıyor.
Here, this one's for you
Al bakalım, bu da seninkisi.
This way, you'll be able to keep playing even after I'm—
Böylelikle ben yokken bile oynamaya devam...
Just stop!
Yeter artık!
You're gonna get better, you hear me? I don't need this thing... I don't want it!
İyileşeceksin, anlıyor musun? Buna ihtiyacım yok... İstemiyorum!
I imagine the Casket of Tomes I gave you
Sana verdiğim Sır Kutusu
Is probably gathering dust in a corner somewhere...
bir köşede toz içindedir herhalde.
So, this is my last gift to you. I'm sorry that I could only give it to you now
Bu sana son hediyem. Ancak verebildiğim için üzgünüm.
Do you remember when we first met?
İlk buluşmamızı hatırlıyor musun?
You were the only one willing to be friends with the kid with Eleazar
Eleazar hastası çocukla bir tek sen arkadaş olmak istemiştin.
Now it's my turn to help you make some new friends
Şimdi arkadaş bulmana yardımcı olma sırası bende.
This way, I'll always be by your side, my friend
Böylelikle hep yanında olabileceğim dostum.